Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Board Consolidated General File, Series II
  - Smythe, Lewis S. C., 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1152)
  - Sontag, Frederick, 1974-1977 (Box 79, Folder 1153)
  - Soochow, Friends of, 1967-1979 (Box 79, Folder 1154)
  - Soochow University (China) - List of graduates of the College of Arts and Sciences, 1948, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1155)
  - 1907-1948
  - Soochow University (China) - Custodial accounts, 1948-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1156)
  - Soulliere, Ellen, 1970-1972 (Box 79, Folder 1157)
  - Southern Illinois University - Tunghai faculty exchange, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1158)
  - Southern Methodist University - Yonsei University exchange program, 1971-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1159)
  - Sovern, James S., 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1160)
  - Sovik, Arne, 1973-1979 (Box 79, Folder 1161)
  - Spaidal, Donald R., 1968-1975 (Box 79, Folder 1161)
  - Speidel, William M. and Edna, 1971-1976 (Box 79, Folder 1162)
  - Spelman, Douglas, 1963-1977 (Box 79, Folder 1163)
  - Spencer Trask Co., 1972-1977 (Box 79, Folder 1164)
  - Sprague Educational and Charitable Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 79, Folder 1165)
  - Stahnke, Arthur, 1970-1972 (Box 79, Folder 1166)
  - Standish, E. Myles, 1967-1979 (Box 79, Folder 1166)
  - Stanwick Library Book Project, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1167)
  - Stange, Paul D., 1969-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1168)
  - Starr Foundation, 1962-1978 (Box 79, Folder 1169)
  - Stearns, Lisa, 1975-1978 (Box 79, Folder 1170)
  - Steeds, Rita, 1969-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1171)
  - Stephens, John U., 1967-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1172)
  - Stillman, Stanley, 1976-1977 (Box 80, Folder 1172)
  - Stine, Esther, 1973-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1173)
  - Stockwell, Eugene L., 1965-1976 (Box 80, Folder 1174)
  - Stonehurst Foundation, 1962-1973 (Box 80, Folder 1175)
  - Stone, W. Clement and Jessie V., 1965-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1176)
  - Stoodley, Bartlett H., 1961-1973 (Box 80, Folder 1177)
  - Stowe, David M., 1971-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1178)
  - Stowe, Everett M., 1966-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1179)
  - Strauss, William L., 1976 (Box 80, Folder 1180)
  - Strout, Alan, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1181)
  - Struthers, Ernest, 1965-1977 (Box 80, Folder 1182)
  - Stuart, John Leighton - Memorial, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 1183)
  - Sumitomo Bank, Ltd., 1973-1975 (Box 80, Folder 1184)
  - Sun Life Assurance Co. of Canada, 1973-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1185)
  - Sundberg, James, 1965-1966 (Box 80, Folder 1186)
  - Surdna Foundation, 1970-1973 (Box 80, Folder 1187)
  - Sutherland, Catharine E. - Estate of, 1977-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1188)
  - Suttmeier, R. Peter, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1189)
  - Swatek, E. Paul, 1964-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1190)
  - Sword, William H., 1965-1977 (Box 80, Folder 1191)
  - Sze, Morgan C., 1967-1979 (Box 80, Folder 1191)
  - Ta - To (Box 80, Folder 1192-1195)
  - Tr - Ty (Box 81, Folder 1196)
  - Taiwan: -General (Box 81, Folder 1197)
  - Taiwan: -Presbyterian Church in Taiwan, 1972-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1198)
  - Taiwan:-Tainan Junior College of Home Economics, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 1199)
  - Taiwan:-Tainan Theological College, 1963-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1200)
  - Taiwan:-Taiwan First Investment Trust Co., Ltd., 1972-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1201)
  - Taiwan:-Taiwan Theological College, 1974-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1202)
  - Talbot, Phillips, 1970-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1203)
  - Tan, Charlotte, 1973-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1204)
  - Tan, Margaret Hee-Leng, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 1204)
  - Tang, Jimmie W. P., 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 1205)
  - Tanner, Susan K., 1963-1966 (Box 81, Folder 1206)
  - Tate, E. Mowbray, 1963-1966 (Box 81, Folder 1207)
  - Taylor, Lloyd A., 1974-1976 (Box 81, Folder 1208)
  - Technical Assistance Information Clearing House, 1977-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1209)
  - Teodoro, Dee Marie and Reynaldo S., 1969-1973 (Box 81, Folder 1210)
  - Thailand Theological Seminary, 1965-1972 (Box 81, Folder 1211)
  - Thelin, Mark C. and Virginia, 1971-1979 (Box 81, Folder 1212)
  - Theological Education Fund, 1972-1977 (Box 81, Folder 1213)
  - Thiergartner, George - Fund, 1964-1970 (Box 81, Folder 1214)
  - Thomas, George F., 1965-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1214)
  - Thomas, T. M., 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1215)
  - Thompson-Travis, Beverley A., 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 1215)
  - Thompson, Kenneth H., 1969-1978 (Box 82, Folder 1216)
  - Thompson, Perry, 1962-1968 (Box 82, Folder 1217)
  - Thorne, Samuel - Estate of, 1962-1967 (Box 82, Folder 1218)
  - Thurber, Newton L., 1965-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1219)
  - Thurston, James N., 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1220)
  - Tiedeman, Trent, 1960-1964 (Box 82, Folder 1221)
  - Tobias, Benjamin C., 1977-1978 (Box 82, Folder 1221)
  - Tompkins, Pauline, 1973-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1222)
  - Towle, Joseph W., 1970-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1223)
  - Towne, Helen L., 1967-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1224)
  - Tredennick, Dorothy W., 1965-1975 (Box 82, Folder 1224)
  - Trimble, A. Theodore, 1959-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1225)
  - Trinity Theological College - Singapore, 1972-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1226)
  - Troyer, Maurice E., 1967-1973 (Box 82, Folder 1226)
  - Trump, Ross M., 1965-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1227)
  - Tsu, Andrew Y. Y., 1961-1973 (Box 82, Folder 1228)
  - Tucker, W. Henry, 1965-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1229)
  - Tucker, Marcia Brady - Foundation, 1964-1972 (Box 82, Folder 1230)
  - Trumbull, Harriet, 1964-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1231)
  - Turk, Marsh, Kelly Hoare, 1962-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1232-1233)
  - Turk, Marsh, Ouchterloney Kelly, 1958-1961 (Box 83, Folder 1234)
  - Turner, John, 1974-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1235-1236)
  - Turner, P. Margaret, 1946-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1237)
  - Tweedy, Gordon B. and Mary, 1970-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1238)
  - Twinem, Marguerite, 1966-1974 (Box 83, Folder 1239)
  - Tye, Norwood and Wilma, 1973-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1240)
  - Tyler, Florence G. - Estate of, 1944-1958 (Box 83, Folder 1241)
  - U (Box 83, Folder 1242)
  - Ulrich, M. Gene, 1968-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1243)
  - Underwood, Lonnie W. and Helen, 1973-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1244)
  - UBCHEA papers: -"The United Board and its Future - A Background Paper" by Paul T. Lauby, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - UBCHEA papers: -Documentation of UBCHEA relationships with other organizations, 1964-1974 (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - UBCHEA papers: -Discussion of UBCHEA name, 1963-1968 (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - UBCHEA papers: -"Notes on the History of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia" by M. Searle Bates, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - UBCHEA papers -Scripts for UBCHEA slide presentations, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - UBCHEA - East Asia Tour, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 1246)
  - United Church of Christ, 1970-1975 (Box 84, Folder 1247)
  - United Church Women of Rochester Vicinity, 1963-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1247)
  - United College of Hong Kong - Library survey (Frick), 1963 (Box 84, Folder 1248)
  - United Ministries in Higher Education, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 1248)
  - United Service to China, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 84, Folder 1249)
  - United States: -Agency for International Development / American Schools Hospitals Abroad, 1972-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1250)
  - United States: -Commerce, Department of, 1972-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1251)
  - United States: -Congress, 1964-1972 (Box 84, Folder 1252)
  - United States: -Internal Revenue Service, 1964-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1253)
  - United States: -Tax Reform Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1254)
  - University of Massachusetts, 1966-1974 (Box 84, Folder 1255)
  - University of Michigan, 1967-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1256)
  - University of Shanghai, 1964-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1257)
  - Unsworth, Richard P., 1964-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1258)
  - V (Box 84, Folder 1259)
  - Vail, Herman L., 1967-1976 (Box 84, Folder 1260)
  - Van Arsdale, May B. - Estate of, 1963-1977 (Box 84, Folder 1261)
  - Van Burkalow, Anastasia, 1967-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1262)
  - Van den Doel, Anthonie, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 1262)
  - Van Dusen, Henry P., 1970-1975 (Box 84, Folder 1263)
  - Van Evera, William P., 1965-1978 (Box 84, Folder 1264)
  - Van Houweling, C. D., 1965-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1265)
  - Van Lierop, Peter, 1964-1978 (Box 84, Folder 1266)
  - Van Loon, Gary, 1974-1979 (Box 84, Folder 1267)
  - Van Ness, Peter, 1962-1965 (Box 84, Folder 1268)
  - Van Vleck, Joseph, Jr., 1973-1976 (Box 84, Folder 1269)
  - Van Winkle, Mrs. John S., 1965-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1270)
  - Van Wyk, Gordon J., 1973-1978 (Box 85, Folder 1270)
  - Varley, H. L., 1966-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1271)
  - Vasantkumar, Nulamotu, 1978-1979 (Box 85, Folder 1272)
  - Vaughn, Walter, 1969-1970 (Box 85, Folder 1273)
  - Vermilya, Mabel W. - Estate of, 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 1274)
  - Vickers, Elizabeth and Frank, 1969-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1275)
  - Vieg, John A. and Elizabeth Lam, 1965-1979 (Box 85, Folder 1276)
  - Viehman, Harold H., 1965-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1276)
  - Vietnam - miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1277)
  - Vikner, David L., 1965-1977 (Box 85, Folder 1278)
  - Vogel, Norman W., 1967-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1279)
  - Volunteers In Asia, Inc., 1979 (Box 85, Folder 1280)
  - Voskuyl, Roger, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 1281)
  - Vrooman, Julia Scott - Estate of, and Carl, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1282)
  - Wa - We (Box 85, Folder 1283-1287)
  - Wh - Wu (Box 86, Folder 1288-1291)
  - Wachowiak, Frank, 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 1292)
  - Wade, Donald V., 1968-1979 (Box 86, Folder 1293)
  - Walker, Egbert H., 1973-1977 (Box 86, Folder 1294)
  - Wang, Jun Chuan, 1964-1978 (Box 86, Folder 1295)
  - Wang, Kung-Lee, 1965-1975 (Box 86, Folder 1296)
  - Wang, Ralph T. P., 1973-1976 (Box 86, Folder 1297)
  - Wantagh Community Church, NY, 1962-1975 (Box 86, Folder 1298)
  - War Claims Coordinating Council, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 1299)
  - War Claims Coordinating Council, 1969-1972 (Box 87, Folder 1300-1301)
  - Ward, Helen A - Estate of, 1961-1962 (Box 87, Folder 1302)
  - Warden, Barbara - Foundation, 1961-1974 (Box 87, Folder 1303)
  - Waring, William Davis, 1966-1967 (Box 87, Folder 1304)
  - Warren Wilson College, NC, 1977-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1304)
  - Washington Committee, 1971-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1305-1307)
  - Watts, Edward E., 1972-1978 (Box 87, Folder 1308)
  - Wead, Katharine H., 1968-1977 (Box 87, Folder 1309)
  - Webb, Christine, 1968-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1309)
  - Webb, H. Eugene, Jr., 1964-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1309)
  - Wegner, Kenneth W. and Grace, 1972-1980 (Box 87, Folder 1310)
  - Wei, Hsioh Ren, 1965-1979 (Box 88, Folder 1311)
  - Wei, Mark, 1973-1979 (Box 88, Folder 1311)
  - Welcher, Amy Ogden, 1964-1980 (Box 88, Folder 1312)
  - Weldy, Dwight E., 1967-1978 (Box 88, Folder 1313)
  - Wellesley College - Career Services Office, 1964-1976 (Box 88, Folder 1314)
  - Wellesley-Yenching, 1944-1979 (Box 88, Folder 1315-1321)
  - West, Harold B. - Foundation, 1964-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1322)
  - West, Charles C., 1972-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1323)
  - West China Union University book, 1964-1976 (Box 89, Folder 1324)
  - West, Philip, 1966-1977 (Box 89, Folder 1325)
  - Westport Presbyterian Church,MO, 1966-1971 (Box 89, Folder 1326)
  - Weter, Winifred E., 1964-1978 (Box 89, Folder 1326)
  - Whallon, Carolyn, 1969-1970 (Box 89, Folder 1327)
  - White, Herbert D., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1327)
  - Whitney, Yenwith, 1968-1978 (Box 89, Folder 1328)
  - Whittemore, Edward L., 1975-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1328)
  - Whittlesey, Charles and Mary, 1976-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1329)
  - Whitworth College, WA, 1967-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1329)
  - Wiant, Bliss, 1964-1976 (Box 89, Folder 1330)
  - Widergren, John F., 1976-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1331)
  - Wilcox, Herbert, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1332)
  - Wilcox, Mabel I., 1965-1977 (Box 89, Folder 1333)
  - Wiles, Arthur P., 1973-1977 (Box 89, Folder 1333)
  - Williams, Haydn, 1971-1976 (Box 89, Folder 1333)
  - Williams, Marjory E., 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1334)
  - Williams, M. O., 1966-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1335)
  - Willis, Leota S., 1961-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1336)
  - Wilson, Brian, 1959-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1337)
  - Wilson, Frederick R., 1971-1978 (Box 89, Folder 1337)
  - Wilson, Stanley D., 1964-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1338)
  - Witwer, J. David, 1965-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1339)
  - Wireman, Billy O., 1967-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1340)
  - Wohl, Julian, 1975-1979 (Box 89, Folder 1341)
  - Wohlers, Lester and Barbara, 1966-1970 (Box 89, Folder 1342)
  - Wolferz, Louis E. and Katharine, Estate of, 1969-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1343)
  - Womack, Robert L., 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1344)
  - Woo, Franklin and Jean, 1976-1979 (Box 90, Folder 1345)
  - Wood, Mary Elizabeth - Foundation, 1960-1979 (Box 90, Folder 1346)
  - Wood, Struthers Winthrop Inc. - corres. and UBCHEA financial reports, 1960-1979 (Box 90, Folder 1347-1351)
  - Workshops: -India - William H. Schecter, 1974-1976 (Box 90, Folder 1352)
  - Workshops: -Indonesia - William H. Schecter, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1353)
  - Workshops: -"The Place of Humanities in Christian Universities in Asia" / 12th Asian Presidents Conference, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1354)
  - Workshops: -Guidance and Counseling - Philippines, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1355)
  - Workshops: -Educational Management Consultancy - Hong Kong, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1356)
  - Workshops: -Water Pollution - Taiwan, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1357)
  - Workshops: -4th Triennial Conference - India, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 1358)
  - Workshops: -Higher Education in S. E. Asia - Singapore, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 1359)
  - Workshops: -Xavier University - Philippines, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 1360)
  - Workshops: -Nursing Education - Philippines, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 1361)
  - Workshops: -Chaplains - Hong Kong, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1362)
  - Workshops: -Institutional Planning and Management - Philippines, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1363)
  - Workshops: -Teaching English as a Foreign Language - Indonesia, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 1364)
  - Workshops: -University Development and Fundraising - Hong Kong, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1365)
  - Workshops: -Vital Role of the University - Korea, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1366)
  - Workshops: -University Management - Hong Kong, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 1367)
  - Workshops: -University Planning and Development - Hong Kong, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1368)
  - Workshops: -Liberal Arts Education - Hong Kong, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 1369)
  - World Council of Churches - Theological Education Fund (see also: Theological Education Fund), 1976 (Box 91, Folder 1370)
  - World Council of Churches - Christian Medical Commission, 1968-1973 (Box 91, Folder 1371)
  - World Day of Prayer, 1958-1971 (Box 91, Folder 1372)
  - World Education, 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 1373)
  - World Student Christian Federation - Asia Office, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 1373)
  - Worship services, 1976-1977, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1374)
  - Wright, Eleanor M. - Memorial fund, 1956-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1375)
  - Wright, Stephen J., 1974-1978 (Box 91, Folder 1375)
  - Wu, Daisy Yen, 1960-1979 (Box 91, Folder 1376)
  - Wu, Ke Lun, 1965-1970 (Box 91, Folder 1377)
  - Wu, Teh Yao, 1971-1978 (Box 91, Folder 1378)
  - X (Box 92, Folder 1379)
  - Ya - Yu (Box 92, Folder 1380-1382)
  - Yale University - misc., 1961-1973 (Box 92, Folder 1383)
  - Yale-China Association, 1964-1979 (Box 92, Folder 1384)
  - Yale - China Records Project, 1967-1973 (Box 92, Folder 1385)
  - Yang, Chia-chi, 1971-1976 (Box 92, Folder 1386)
  - Yeh, Tze, 1967-1975 (Box 92, Folder 1387)
  - Yenching University - Bequests and trusts, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 1388)
  - Yenching Alumni Association, 1958-1979 (Box 92, Folder 1389-1391)
  - Yenching alumni claim against Yenching fund held by UBCHEA, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 1392)
  - Yolton Memorial Fund, 1958-1972 (Box 92, Folder 1393)
  - Yonsei Alumni Association, 1966-1977 (Box 92, Folder 1394)
  - Youlster, James Saxon, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 1395)
  - Young, Ching Chang, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 1396)
  - Young, David P., 1975-1978 (Box 92, Folder 1397-1398)
  - Young, David P., 1979 (Box 93, Folder 1399)
  - Young, Herrick B., 1972-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1400)
  - Young, In Eung, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 1401)
  - Yu, Frederick T. C., 1967-1974 (Box 93, Folder 1402)
  - Yu, Marina Su-chih, 1958-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1403)
  - Yu, Tsai-fan, 1965-1979 (Box 93, Folder 1404)
  - Yu, Wei-liang, 1970-1977 (Box 93, Folder 1405)
  - Yuan, Heh-hsiang, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1405)
  - Z (Box 93, Folder 1406)
  - Zeldin, Barbara and Jesse, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 1407)
  - Zen, Wei-tz, 1958-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1407)
  - Zosa, Evangelina, 1976-1978 (Box 93, Folder 1408)
- New File, Series III
  - Administrative
    - By-laws and Constitution
      - Documents, FY 1973-1979 (Box 94, Folder 1409)
    - Board of Trustees
      - Budgets, FY 1967-1979 (Box 94, Folder 1410)
      - Counsellors correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 94, Folder 1411)
      - Membership lists, 1955-1975 (Box 94, Folder 1412)
      - Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1413-1415)
      - Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 95, Folder 1416-1421)
      - Minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 1422-1427)
      - Minutes, Executive Session, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 1428)
      - Reports, 1962-1974 (Box 96, Folder 1429)
      - Trustee Consultation, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 1430)
    - Standing Committees
      - Development Committee, 1971-1980 (Box 97, Folder 1431-1434)
      - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 97, Folder 1435-1437)
      - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 98, Folder 1438-1439)
      - Executive Committee: Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 98, Folder 1440)
      - Executive Committee: Sub-Committee on Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 98, Folder 1441)
      - Finance Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1965-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1442-1448)
      - Finance Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1970-1980 (Box 99, Folder 1449-1458)
      - Finance Committee: External Audits, 1972-1980 (Box 99, Folder 1459)
      - Finance Committee: Monthly Statements, 1971-1976 (Box 100, Folder 1460-1464)
      - Finance Committee: Monthly Statements, 1976-1979 (Box 101, Folder 1465-1467)
    - Specialized Committees
      - China Claims Committee, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 1468)
      - College and Society Committee, 1963-1974 (Box 102, Folder 1469-1471)
      - Fellowships Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 102, Folder 1472-1474)
      - Investment and Banking Committee, 1969-1979 (Box 103, Folder 1475-1477)
      - Medical Education Committee, 1957-1974 (Box 103, Folder 1478-1479)
      - Personnel Resources Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 103, Folder 1480-1484)
      - Personnel Resources Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 104, Folder 1485-1486)
      - University Outreach Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 104, Folder 1487-1489)
      - University Life Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 104, Folder 1490)
      - University Programs Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 104, Folder 1491-1495)
    - Miscellaneous Committees
      - Agenda Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 105, Folder 1496)
      - China Concerns Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 105, Folder 1497-1498)
      - Endowment Study Task Force (Ad Hoc Committee), 1972 (Box 105, Folder 1499)
      - Five Year Plan Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1500-1501)
      - Five Year Relationships Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1502)
      - Japan Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 1503)
      - New Directions and Wider Areas of Service, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 1504)
      - Nominations Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1505-1507)
      - Policy Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 106, Folder 1508-1509)
      - Purpose, Function and Stucture (Committee on), 1973 (Box 106, Folder 1510)
      - Research and Publications Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 1511)
      - Restructuring Sub-Committee, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 1511)
      - Search Committee (Presidential), 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 1512)
      - Social Responsibility for Investments (Committee on), 1978-1979 (Box 106, Folder 1513)
      - University Programs, Project Summaries, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 1514)
  - Publicity/ Reports
    - Material re. Communist takeover: [Material collected by New York office regarding Communist takeover of mainland colleges. Includes corres. from "Committee of Nine", Bliss Wiant, William P. Fenn, Ruth M. Chester, Wu Yi Fang, Francis (C.M.) Wei, T.H. Wang, Elsie Priest, John S. Barr, George B. Cressey, C.T. Yung, Margaret Tucker, G.F. Riggs], 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1515)
    - Newspaper clippings re. China colleges, 1948-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1516)
- College Files, Series IV
  The files for each of these institutions are generally in an alphabetically arranged "consolidated general file", as received. In some cases there is also an "administrative file" which includes material not already incorporated into the consolidated general file.
  - Hong Kong
    - Chung Chi College
      - Hong Kong Bill, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 1521)
      - Li, Choh-ming (Box 107, Folder 1522)
      - Ordinances and statutes, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1523)
      - A - F (Box 107, Folder 1524)
      - Consultation report, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 1525)
      - Finance, 1975-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1526)
      - Information questionnaire, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 1527)
      - Kwong, Luke, 1976-1979 (Box 107, Folder 1528)
      - Library, 1976-1979 (Box 107, Folder 1529)
      - M - R (Box 107, Folder 1530)
      - Ng, Lee Ming, 1976-1978 (Box 107, Folder 1531)
      - Proposal applications for U.B. grants, 1976-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1532)
      - Rayne, Robert N., 1967-1978 (Box 107, Folder 1533)
      - Overseas personnel lists, 1975-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1534)
      - S - Z (Box 107, Folder 1535)
      - Scholarships from United Board, 1973-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1536-1537)
      - Seal, motto, song, 1954-1955 (Box 107, Folder 1538)
      - Shen, Philip, 1973-1979 (Box 107, Folder 1539)
      - Tam, S. W., 1973-1979 (Box 108, Folder 1540-1541)
      - Theology Division, 1977-1978 (Box 108, Folder 1542)
      - Turner-Smith, Roland, 1975-1977 (Box 108, Folder 1543)
      - Wellesley-Yenching Jr. Fellowship recipients: Mary Petite, Ann Rutledge, 1976-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1544-1545)
      - Yue, K. K. (Bursar), 1971-1973 (Box 108, Folder 1546)
      - Yung, C. T., 1971-1975 (Box 108, Folder 1547)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College
      - President's Report, 1978-1980 (Box 108, Folder 1548)
      - Background, Profile, Historical, 1967-1969 (Box 108, Folder 1549)
      - Budget Requests, 1977-1978 (Box 108, Folder 1550)
      - Chan, Jachin Y., 1976-1977 (Box 108, Folder 1551)
      - Chinese Christian Universities Alumni Association, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 1552)
      - Finance/Disbursements, 1976-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1553)
      - "Green Paper" materials, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 1554)
      - Loan agreement, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 1555)
      - Overseas personnel, 1975-1979 (Box 109, Folder 1556)
      - Proposals, 1975-1976, 1979-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1557-1558)
      - Reports, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 1559)
      - Tse, Daniel, 1968-1979 (Box 109, Folder 1560-1563)
      - Water pollution, 1977-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1564)
      - Yu, Timothy, 1971-1974 (Box 109, Folder 1565)
  - Indonesia
    - Petra Christian University
      - Book requisitions, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 1566)
      - Overseas list, 1975-1977 (Box 110, Folder 1567)
      - Patty, O. F., 1974-1979 (Box 110, Folder 1568-1569)
      - Proposals, Grants, reports, 1976-1980 (Box 110, Folder 1570)
      - Reports (Consulting), 1973-1974 (Box 110, Folder 1571)
      - Reports (Financial, etc.), 1971-1979 (Box 110, Folder 1572)
      - Schechter, W. H. [see: Reports (Consulting)]
    - Satya Wacana Christian University
      - Adam, Hurhadi, 1971-1978 (Box 110, Folder 1573)
      - A.S.H.A./Aid Grant, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 1574)
      - Agriculture, Faculty of, 1967-1972 (Box 110, Folder 1575)
      - Andoko, Setiawan, 1973-1975 (Box 110, Folder 1576)
      - Background/History (Box 111, Folder 1577)
      - Beechy, Atlee, 1976-1978 (Box 111, Folder 1578)
      - Buildings: Faculty Housing, 1972-1976 (Box 111, Folder 1579)